Oh, my God.
That dream again.
Kujo, Jotaro, age 17.
Height, six foot four.
His father's Japanese, a jazz musician,
is currently on an overseas concert tour.
His British-American mother visits
every day to try and persuade him.
Oh, and there are a countless number
of personal items inside of his cell.
Move out!
Hey!
Those gang members, just punks.
But he put eight of them
in the hospital by himself.
Despite that fact, we've
told them he's free to go.
Why does he refuse to leave? He's a demon!
Squatting in a place like this,
what is he trying to accomplish?
Papa, it's Holly.
Papa, please help me.
What's wrong, Holly?
Actually, it's Jotaro.
He had a run-in with
some local gang members,
got into a fight, and
was thrown into jail.
The police officer told me that
they'll release him and that
I should make him stay home
to reflect on what he's done.
But he refuses to leave
until he discovers the
true nature of the evil
spirit that haunts him.
Evil spirit?
Calm down, Holly.
You're certain that Jotaro
said evil spirit? Mm-hmm.
I'm sure of it, Papa.
Right.
Don't worry, Holly.
I'll fly over right away to help you.
Thank you, Papa.
Papa!
You're going home for sure today, Cujo.
Don't worry.
My grandson is coming with me.
Grandson?
Damned woman.
You even dragged that old man into this.
What a pain.
Now, Jotaro, don't you dare
address your mother that way.
Not ever.
And is that the attitude you have
towards your own grandfather after
I've come all the way from New York
for the first time in ten years?
Is it?
Out.
You're coming home with me.
I didn't ask for you.
Just get lost.
Jotaro, please listen to him.
I'm sure your grandfather
can help you with this.
So you think you can help me, huh?
You do not understand the terrible
nature of this evil spirit.
How could he have...
Oh, oh, oh, oh,
oh.
I don't know.
Another hand, it came out of
Jotaro and stopped the bullet.
You could see that hand too, Holly?
Yes.
Any strange sensations?
No, not really.
That's good.
I think we'll just step outside
and leave this matter to you.
How strange.
I wonder if we were the only
ones who could see that hand.
I'll explain it all later, Holly.
Right now, we have to get
Jotaro out of this cell.
Old man, you don't get it.
I'm staying right here.
Just take this, and then run along home.
Huh? What? What the?
My artificial hand.
Incredible.
He managed to make a fool out of me.
I have to admit, though, his abilities
are greater than I ever imagined.
However, I don't think he'll
be convinced by words alone.
No.
To force him to prepare for
the danger he's going to face,
Jotaro must be made to
understand physically.
It's your turn.
I met my friend Avdol here
three years ago in Egypt.
Avdol, force my grandson
Jotaro out of this cage.
Mr.
Jostar, I may have to be
a little rough with him.
I don't care.
Do what you have to.
It's no use.
You may be strong, but
there's no way you can win.
Papa, what is he going to do?
What? What the?
Yes, that thing you call an evil spirit.
Avdol has one as well.
Avdol's will controls this evil spirit.
Its name is Magician's Red.
An evil spirit you can
control with your will.
That's right.
The evil spirit can be controlled.
Ah, so at last it reveals
its full form to us.
I did not think he could
materialize it so well.
Mr. Joestar.
I tried to go easy on him.
But he is more powerful than I thought.
There is a chance my life is at risk.
If you still insist on having me
force your grandson out of there,
he may end up in the hospital.
Go ahead.
Grant! Fine!
Papa!
Jotaro is...
Hey, Garth!
What the hell is going on?
It's hot!
What could they possibly
be doing to cause this?
I can't breathe.
If you weaken, the evil spirit weakens.
Chotaro, the true nature of
what you call an evil spirit
is a manifestation of the
power of your life energy.
From the way it appears and stands
beside you, we call this vision a stand.
Hmm, how's that?
Now will you step out of that cage?
Enough already.
Keep this up and you're
gonna pay with your life.
What?
What the hell?
The iron bars are bending
all by themselves!
Whoa!
Why did you turn away from me?
Mr. Joestar.
It's done.
He's no longer in the cage.
Hmm?
It looks like I've been outwitted.
That is not true.
I intended to have you
leave here on a stretcher.
However, your stand's power
was greater than I expected.
What if...
this so-called stand of mine had
actually thrown that iron bar at you?
Just what would you have done then?
A flimsy iron bar like that.
Magician's Red would have
vaporized that bar in mid-air.
Just that simple.
Chodro,
your stand is a special
power that has awakened
because you're going to need it very soon.
I'll explain it all to you later.
Right, let's go.
Listen carefully, Chotaro.
So, this is the story of the destiny
bestowed upon the Joestar family.
About four years ago, in the Atlantic
Ocean off the coast of Africa,
a
sturdy iron casket was
salvaged from a shipwreck
on the ocean floor my grandfather jonathan
joestar died on the
passenger ship that was
transporting the casket
that much has been confirmed
but
when it was found and opened
there was nothing inside?
But,
I'm absolutely certain that
it once contained the body
of the man that Avdol and
I are still searching for.
Hold on.
You're trying to tell
me this guy's body was
at the bottom of the
ocean for a hundred years?
I don't get it.
You've been talking about this guy
as if you think he's still alive.
Yes,
I believe that man, the very incarnation
of evil, is alive and walking among us.
He has awakened from
his hundred-year sleep.
His name is Dio.
We must seek out and destroy
this man at all costs.
It is our destiny.
Holly, did you find what I asked for?
Oh, yes.
But what are you going
to do with it, Papa?
Actually,
about a year ago, I discovered that a
stand ability had developed in me as well.
What do you mean by that?
My stand ability...
is this!
There. Did you see that?
Those brambles that appeared.
That was my stand ability.
Hermit purple, it transfers
visions onto film.
Psychography,
the image that is about to appear on
that film, will determine your destiny.
Holly, please show us what's on the
left side of the nape of your neck.
Jotaro, you too.
This star-shaped birthmark
is the star of our destiny,
which the Joestar family cannot escape.
My mother told me that my father,
who died when I was still a child,
had that birthmark as well.
What does this birthmark have to
do with that psychography of yours?
Well, it's about time.
That is Dio.
He's the only one who
ever appears on the film.
And look at the birthmark
on the nape of his neck.
It shows that the bastard's body,
from the neck down, is my grandfather.
Jonathan Joestar's body
which Dio has taken over.
Again...
Once again, I sensed that
someone was watching me.
Could it be Jonathan's descendants?
Is it possible this body is sending
some signals to his descendants?
That man, at this very moment,
He's hiding somewhere in the
world and searching for something.
Four years have gone by since then.
The fact that Mai and Jotaro's
stands both appeared within
one year probably has something
to do with Dio's resurrection.
Our stand abilities are what
the world would refer to as ESP.
I was somehow born with these abilities,
but your stands are
connected to Dio's body.
In other words, you are linked to
Jonathan's body by invisible threads.
Probably Dio's existence brought
forth your latent powers.
Avdol, from this photograph, can you
determine where Dio is hiding right now?
I cannot.
But, as before, the background
shows only darkness.
If only I could see through that darkness.
Hold on a sec.
It seems to have found something.
Oh.
A fly? What? What?
You found a fly somewhere
in that darkness?
In any case,
let's send this to the
Speedwagon Foundation
right away so they can
investigate this fly.
Mr. Joestar,
this may help us narrow down the number of
places where Dio could
be hiding right now.
Hmm
Holly, please fax this right away.
Yes, I will
The Hermit card. Wisdom.
Wariness.
Esotericism.
The Magician card. The
Questioner. Diplomacy.
And the key is this one,
the star card, Hope, Jotaro.
Let's go.
Thank you.